http://www.graw.de/overview/data-privacy/

COMPANYWho is GRAWGRAW in 125 wordsRange of servicesLocationsGRAW worldwideCompany historyPhilosophyMission & VisionCorporate PolicyCSR codeSocial commitmentMembershipsEnvironmental impact of radiosondesQualityQuality assuranceCertificatesConflict minerals statementPRODUCTSRadiosondesDFM-17DFM-09PS-15GRAWMET softwareGRAWgo cloud-based analysesGroundstation equipmentGS-EGS-BGS-UAntennas and antenna systemsAntennasTripodsAccessoriesSO-2SO-3UW3UW1ReferencesNEWSTrade FairsPressSERVICEService & SupportGRAW worldwideDownloadsTutorialsCAREERYour Career at GRAWApplication processCONTACTGRAW worldwideContact form
ENDECOMPANYWho is GRAWGRAW in 125 wordsRange of servicesLocationsGRAW worldwideCompany historyPhilosophyMission & VisionCorporate PolicyCSR codeSocial commitmentMembershipsEnvironmental impact of radiosondesQualityQuality assuranceCertificatesConflict minerals statementPRODUCTSRadiosondesDFM-17DFM-09PS-15GRAWMET softwareGRAWgo cloud-based analysesGroundstation equipmentGS-EGS-BGS-UAntennas and antenna systemsAntennasTripodsAccessoriesSO-2SO-3UW3UW1ReferencesNEWSTrade FairsPressSERVICEService & SupportGRAW worldwideDownloadsTutorialsCAREERYour Career at GRAWApplication processCONTACTGRAW worldwideContact form
Graw RadiosondesData Privacy
Data PrivacyThe GRAW Radiosondes GmbH & Co.KG as owner of these websites take the protection of your personal information very seriously. We process personal data collected on our websites according to the regulations of the Bundesdatenschutzgesetz (BDSG) and the Telemediengesetz (TMG). From these data, statistics will be generated which help us to improve our websites to fit your needs. A reference to your person can only be derived, if you have registered yourself directly on our website or if you access our website from a personalised website. A data transfer to third parties, even in excerpts, does not take place under any circumstances.Concerning the data protection law the responsible authority is:GRAW Radiosondes GmbH & Co.KGMuggenhofer Str. 9590429 NurembergGermanyPhone: +49 911 3201-100Fax: +49 911 3201-150E-Mail: info(at)graw.deData protection officerYou may contact our external hired data protection officer for any questions concerning data privacy:External data privacy officerMrs. Gisela PöllingerDatenschutz Pöllinger GmbHDresdner Str.38, 92318 Neumarkt i.d.Opf.Phone: +49 9181/270577-0E-mail: datenschutz(at)datenschutz-poellinger.deWeb: www.datenschutz-poellinger.deWhat are personal data and what we use them forPersonal data is any information about your person that enables an identification, e. g. surname, first name, address or e-mail address. You do not have to disclose personal data to use our websites. If personal data is collected (e. g. surname, postal address or e-mail address in the contact form) this is done always on a voluntary basis whenever possible. We only store data that you transmitted automatically or voluntarily. These data will not be transferred to third parties without your express permission.Information obligation when collecting personal data from the person concernedPlease read the following document concerning our information obligation according to Sec. 13 and 14 GDPR when collecting personal data:Download information obligation document for customers, interested parties and suppliersDownload information obligation document for video MonitoringDownload information obligation document for applicants (German version)SSL encryptionWe use an encryption process in line with state of the art technology via HTTPS (SSL) in order to protect your data during Transmission.Data minimisationWe save personal data according to the principle of data avoidance and minimisation only for as long as it is necessary or prescribed by the legislators (statutory data retention period). If the purpose for the data processing no longer applies or the legally prescribed term ends, the data will be deleted or blocked.We would like to point out that the transmission of data on the Internet (e. g. by communicating via e-mail) may contain security gaps. It is not possible to provide complete data security against access by third parties. Changes and necessary adaptions to legal provisionsWe retain the right to make changes at any time when necessary to ensure that our privacy statement is always up to date with the legally prescribed terms. This shall also apply if the data privacy has to be adapted e. g. in case of new or updated services. The new data privacy is then valid the next time you visit our websites.Data Privacy Statement for the use of MatomoThis website uses the functions of the Matomo Web Analysis Service. Matomo uses so-called "cookies". These are text files that are stored on your computer and enable analysis of your use of the website. To enable this, the usage information created by the cookies (including your shortened IP address) is transferred to our server and stored for analysing purposes to optimise our website. Your IP address is anonymised immediately during this process and you remain anonymous for us. The usage information created by the cookies will not be transferred to third parties. You may refuse the use of cookies by adjusting your browser software appropriately. However, we point out that, in this case, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of the functions of this website. (Source: www.datenschutzbeauftragter-info.de)Data protection declaration for the use of YouTubeThis website uses the function of embedded videos on YouTube. When a website with embedded videos is called up, your IP address is normally already sent to YouTube and cookies are saved on your computer. With our YouTube videos, we have activated the additional data protection mode. This means that in accordance with the data protection declaration from Google, personal data will not be analysed, unless you watch the video. In this case your IP address will be transmitted to YouTube. If you are also logged in to YouTube, this information will also be assigned to your user account.Disclosure, Deletion, BlockingYou have the right at any time to disclosure, at no cost to you, concerning your saved personally identifiable information, its origin and recipients, the purpose of such data processing, as well as a right to correction, blocking, or deletion of this information. In this and in other questions about the topic of personally identifiable information, you may turn to us at any time using the address listed in our Imprint. Server Log FilesThe provider of these pages automatically collects and stores information in so-called server log files, which your browser automatically transmits to us. These are:IP addressPage, from which the file was requestedDate, timeBrowser type and browser settingsOperating systemThe page you have visitedData volume transmittedAccess status (file transmitted, file not found etc.)These data cannot be linked to specific persons. No consolidation of these data with other data sources is performed. We reserve the right to subsequently inspect these data should specific evidence of unlawful use become apparent to us. CookiesThese Internet pages sometimes use so-called cookies. Cookies do no harm to your computer and do not contain viruses. Cookies are used to make our offering more user-friendly, more effective, and safer. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer and which your browser stores.Most of the cookies we use are so-called "session cookies". They are automatically deleted after the end of your visit. Other cookies remain stored on your terminal until you delete them. These cookies allow us to recognize your browser on your next visit.You can adjust your browser so that you will be informed about the placing of cookies and only allow cookies in individual cases, accept cookies only in specific cases or exclude them generally, and activate the automatic deletion of cookies when you close your browser. The deactivation of cookies may limit the functionality of this website. Contact FormWhen you send us enquiries using the contact form, your data from the contact form, including the contact information you provide, will be stored by us to process your inquiry as well as any follow-up enquiries. We will not disclose this information without your permission to any third parties. Objection of advertising e-mailsThe use of contact data, disclosed as part of the legal obligations applicable to the Imprint, for purposes of transmitting advertising and informational materials not expressly requested, is hereby rejected. The operators of these pages expressly reserve the right to take legal action in the case of unsolicited sending of advertising information, for example spam emails.Legal basis of processingSec. 6 I lit. a EU-GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) is used by our company as the legal basis for processing procedures, for which we obtain consent for a certain processing purpose. If the processing of personal data is necessary to satisfy a contract, where one of the contracting parties is the person concerned, as is for example the case for processing procedures required for a delivery of goods or to provide a service or consideration, then processing is based on Sec. 6 I lit. b EU-GDPR. This also applies to such processing procedures, which are required to implement pre-contractual measures, such as in cases of inquiries about our products or services. If our company is subject to a legal obligation through which processing of personal data becomes necessary, such as to satisfy tax obligations, then processing is based on Sec. 6 I lit. c EU-GDPR. In rare cases the processing of personal data might become necessary to protect the vital interests of the person concerned or another individual. This would for example be the case if a visitor to our company is injured and then would have to give his name, age, health insurance data or other vital information to a doctor, hospital or other third party. Then the processing would be based on Sec. 6 I lit. d EU-GDPR. Lastly processing procedures might be based on Sec. 6 I lit. f EU-GDPR. Processing procedures are based on this legal basis if they are not included in any of the above-mentioned legal bases, if processing is necessary to preserve a justified interest of our company or a third party, insofar as the interests, fundamental rights and basic freedoms of the person concerned do not outweigh other concerns. Such processing procedures are permitted in particular because they were mentioned specifically by the European legislator. The latter represented the opinion to this extent that a justified interest might be assumed if the person concerned is a customer of the responsible person (recital 47 Clause 2 EU-GDPR).
